Seven years in Folsom. In the hole for three.
你在Folsom监狱七年 单独囚禁三年
McNeil before that.
之前在McNeil监狱
McNeil as tough as they say?
那儿真的像所说的那么凶残吗
You looking to become a penologist?
你想做监狱学者吗
You looking to go back?
你想再坐牢
You know, I chased down some crews; guys just looking to fuck up get busted back.
我抓过不少臭名昭著的坏蛋   他们刚一冒头就被我逮个正着抓回去
That you?
你是不是
You must've worked some dipsh*t crews.
跟你打交道的肯定是些笨贼
I worked all kinds.
我跟各种各样的罪犯打交道
You see me doing liquor store holdups with a "Born to Lose" tattoo on my chest?
你看我像是胸前有   坏痞子   纹身 专门打劫烟酒店的小混混吗
No, I do not.
不   你不像
Right. I am never going back.
没错   我再也不会回去了(监狱)
Then don't take down scores.
那就别做傻事
I do what I do best.
我只做我自己擅长的事
I take scores. You do what you do best: try to stop guys like me.
我身手了得   你做你擅长的   试着阻止我这样的人